annegeddes.com 2008-06-17

# Designer baby clothes and baby pictures by Anne Geddes

Your right to privacy is our number one concern. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to annegeddes.com and an explanation of how that information is used. Our policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our visitors at all times. Visiting this website should be a rewarding experience where you feel confident and secure about the information you share with us. If you have additional questions or would like further information on privacy issues, please feel free to contact us. 

### How do we collect or receive your information?

There are two categories of information we collect about you when you visit our site. 

The first type of information we collect about you is personally identifiable information required as part of the site's membership process. Membership is completely optional and is not a prerequisite of using the site. Our site's membership form requires users to give us contact information like your name, country of origin and email address. You have the option to provide us with additional information like birthday, address and gender. By registering you will receive an enhanced and personalized experience when visiting the site. Further, you will receive email newsletters and alerts from us. 

There are other instances where we collect personally identifiable information. However, at all times, you have the option of choosing whether or not to reveal such personal information to us. Examples of when you may voluntarily submit this kind of information include when you sign the Guestbook, or send us feedback or questions.

The second category of information we collect is non-personally identifiable information, in the form of log files. These files enable the generation of broad demographic statistics. Information such as the number of unique visitors, number of visitors from a particular country, the most popular pages and downloads allow us to gain a better understanding of site development needs and visitor trends so that we can improve our website and your annegeddes.com experience. Information gathered from log files is not used in association with any personal details you may divulge.

### What happens with this information?

Annegeddes.com does not and will never rent, sell, or exchange personally identifiable information about its visitors.

The only parties who have access to such information are those employees within the Anne Geddes family of businesses who need it to do their jobs. Our employees are educated about the policies and practices in regard to safeguarding customer information, preventing its unauthorized access, use or disclosure and ensuring its proper handling.

Any third parties that need access to our site for operational or other support services must agree to safeguard your information in strict compliance with our policy. We may, under rare circumstances, provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law. We may also disclose customer information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

### What are "Cookies" and how are they used on this site?

Cookies are small pieces of information (or identifiers) which our website can send to your browser to be stored on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes to facilitate your next visit to our site. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. Cookies can help us to tailor our website to better match your needs and interests, and allow us to better understand how visitors use our site, which, in turn, helps us to focus our resources on improving the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find them at most major websites.

### So what does a cookie do for me, the visitor?

There are several immediate advantages that you can see through the use of cookies. For example, those people who choose to register their details will be greeted with a personalized message on their return visits to our website. There are also a number of intelligent elements that have been built into the site for your enhanced enjoyment. For example, there is a cookie that will track which images you have seen, and with each return visit, will present a new image for your enjoyment.

### Can I disable these cookies?

Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. In most instances, you will find this function within the internet options under tools or the preferences section which is usually found under Edit or Tools. If you do elect to disable annegeddes.com cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience at this site.

### Why do I need to know this?

We want you to know why we ask you to accept a cookie and we want to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you. We know that a lot of people have concerns about cookies, but in talking with many of our users, we feel that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. We value the relationships we have with our visitors, so we respect these concerns.

### How do I opt-out of receiving emails from the site?

Our site requires you to voluntarily opt-in to receive any information from us. We also provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving any future communications at any time. If you want to remove your information from our database and not receive future communications or registration-required service(s), please click here.

### How do I contact the website about privacy issues?

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Website's privacy policy, you should contact the company as follows:

Privacy Policy Coordinator,  
Kel Geddes Management Ltd.,  
2 York Street, Parnell  
Auckland  
New Zealand 

**USA**  
Tel: +1 206 374 9200 

**United Kingdom**  
Tel: +44 20 7651 1500 

**New Zealand** Tel: +64 9 375-2566

### What is the privacy policy covering children (under 13 years of age)?

No information should be submitted to or posted on this site by visitors under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. We will not knowingly accept personal information from children under 13 years of age.

### What is the privacy policy covering teens (people 13-17 years of age)?

Visitors between 13 and 17 years of age are encouraged to make their parent or guardian aware of their membership and involvement in this site.

### How secure is the Internet?

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. We aim to utilize the latest available technology to ensure the highest level of privacy and security for our visitors.

### Your acceptance of these terms 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Privacy Policy of this website. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes.
